Finding Aid for the Daniel C. Prince Papers and S.T.A.R. Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Organizations & Events
  - Organizations & Events – Galerie atelier Herenplaats (Box 37, File 5)
  - Galleries – A-B (Box 37, File 6)
  - Galleries – C (Box 37, File 7)
  - Galleries – D – La Galerie Imaginaire (Box 37, File 8)
  - Galleries – La Galerie 1900*2000 – La Galerie Poche – La Galerie St. Etienne (Box 37, File 9)
  - Galleries – Garrison Art Center – Lake Front SRO Corp. (Box 37, File 10)
  - Galleries – L.A. Louver (Box 37, File 11)
- Organizations & Events
  - Galleries – LewAllen/Butler Fine Art – N (Box 38, File 1)
  - Galleries – O-P (Box 38, File 2)
  - Galleries – R (Box 38, File 3)
  - Galleries – S-T (Box 38, File 4)
  - Galleries – U- Wendy (Box 38, File 5)
  - Galleries – Whiteley Gallery – Z (Box 38, File 6)
  - Galleries – Assorted (Box 38, File 7)
  - Galleries – Film & Theater Presentations (Box 38, File 8)
  - Organizations & Events – GRACE (Grass Roots Arts & Community Events) (Box 38, File 9)
  - Organizations & Events – House of Blues (Box 38, File 10)
  - Organizations & Events – International Children’s Art Museum (Box 38, File 11)
  - Organizations & Events – The Jargon Society (Box 38, File 12)
  - Organizations & Events – The John F. Kennedy Center, Vanderbilt University (Box 38, File 13)
- Organizations & Events
  - Organizations & Events – Loft Artist Association (Box 39, File 1)
  - Organizations & Events – Loft Artist Association (Box 39, File 2)
  - Organizations & Events – Loft Artist Association, Meeting Minutes (Box 39, File 3)
  - Organizations & Events – Loft Artist Association, Clippings (Box 39, File 4)
  - Organizations & Events – Loft Artist Association, Publicity (Box 39, File 5)
  - Organizations & Events – Manhattan Psychiatric Center (Box 39, File 6)
  - Organizations & Events – Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 39, File 7)
  - Museums – American Folk Art Museum (Box 39, File 8)
  - Museums and Art Centers – American Folklife Center, Library of Congress (Box 39, File 9)
  - Museums and Art Centers – American Folklife Center, Library of Congress, Newsletter Vol. VI No 3, Vol. IX No 1, Vol. X No 1-No 4 (Box 39, File 10)
  - Museums and Art Centers – American Folklife Center, Library of Congress, Newsletter Vol. XI No 1- No 3, Vol. XII No 2- No 4, Vol. XIII No 2- No 3, Vol. XIV No1 (Box 39, File 11)
  - Museums and Art Centers – American Visionary Art Museum (Box 39, File 12)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Customs House Museum and Arts Center (Box 39, File 13)
  - Museums and Art Centers – High Art Museum (Box 39, File 14)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Joslyn Art Museum (Box 39, File 15)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Katonah Museum of Art (Box 39, File 16)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Massachusetts Museum of Contemporary Art (Box 39, File 17)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Milwaukee Art Museum (Box 39, File 18)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Museum of American Political Life (Box 39, File 19)
  - Museums and Art Centers – San Diego Museum of Art (Box 39, File 20)
- Organizations & Events
  - Museums and Art Centers – Smithsonian Museums, General (Box 40, File 1)
  - Museums and Art Centers – Smithsonian Museums, National Museum of American Art Symposium (Box 40, File 2)
  - Museums American Art and Art Centers – Whitney Museum of (Box 40, File 3)
  - Museums and Art Centers – A-G (Box 40, File 4)
  - Museums and Art Centers – H-L (Box 40, File 5)
  - Museums and Art Centers – M-R (Box 40, File 6)
  - Museums and Art Centers – S-W (Box 40, File 7)
  - Museums and Art Centers – College/University Museums A-E (Box 40, File 8)
  - Museums and Art Centers – College/University Museums F-S (Box 40, File 9)
  - Museums and Art Centers – College/University Museums U-W (Box 40, File 10)
  - NIAD (National Institute of Art and Disabilities) (Box 40, File 11)
  - Outlook Nashville (Box 40, File 12)
  - Outsider Art Fair (Box 40, File 13)
- Organizations & Events
  - Popular Culture Association and American Culture Association, Annual meeting, 1984 (Box 41, File 1)
  - St. Sophi’s (Box 41, File 2)
- Writings, Articles
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, American Art Review, Dec. 1994 - Jan. 1995 (Box 41, File 3)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Bibliography (Box 41, File 4)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Correspondence (Box 41, File 5)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Drafts and Edits (Box 41, File 6)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Drafts and Edits (Box 41, File 7)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Illustrations (Box 41, File 8)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Research (Box 41, File 9)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Drafts (Box 41, File 10)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Drafts with Revisions (Box 41, File 11)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Edits and Notes (Box 41, File 12)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Foot Notes (Box 41, File 13)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Illustration Inserts (Box 41, File 14)
  - Writings, Articles - “A Good Likeness: Techniques in Self Taught Portraiture”, Research Notes (Box 41, File 15)
  - Writings, Articles - Environments in Crisis by Dan Prince, Clarion, Dec. 1987 (Box 41, File 16)
  - Writings, Articles - Environments in Crisis by Dan Prince, Clarion, Dec. 1987 (Box 41, File 17)
- Writings, Articles
  - Writings, Articles –Hawaiian Petroglyphs, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Mar 1, 1982 (Box 42, File 1)
  - Writings, Articles –Hawaiian Petroglyphs, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Mar 1, 1982 (Box 42, File 2)
  - Writings, Articles –Hawaiian Petroglyphs, Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 3)
  - Writings, Articles – Hearts of Shells, Daniel C. Prince, Americana, Jan/Feb 1982 pp 40-42 (Box 42, File 4)
  - Writings, Articles – Howard Finsters’ Paradise Garden: A Plan for the Future, Daniel C. Prince The Clarion 1988 Vol. 13 no 1 (Box 42, File 5)
  - Writings, Articles – Inuit Art: Light on the Arctic, Daniel C. Prince AirCal, Jan 1984 pp 16-20 (Box 42, File 6)
  - Writings, Articles – Narrative Art (Box 42, File 7)
  - Writings, Articles – Preservation of Folk Art Environments: Techniques and Case Histories (Box 42, File 8)
  - Writings, Articles – Scrimshaw: Carving of the Yankee Sailor, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Jul 31 (Box 42, File 9)
  - Writings, Articles – Scrimshaw: Art of the Yankee Whaler, Daniel C. Prince Art and Antiques, May/June 1981 pp 108-112 (Box 42, File 10)
- Writings, Lectures
  - Writings, Lectures – Crosscurrents of Modern English (a proposal for a lecture course) (Box 42, File 11)
  - Writings, Lectures – Notes (Box 42, File 12)
  - Writings, Lectures – San Diego Museum of Art, notes (Box 42, File 13)
  - Writings, Lectures – Folk Environment lecture (Box 42, File 14)
  - Writings, Lectures – Cheekwood (Box 42, File 15)
- Writings, Manuscripts
  - Writings, Manuscripts - A Dangerous Job, Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 16)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - An Increment of Excrement (Film), Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 17)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - Appreciation: Folk/Environment Overview (Box 42, File 18)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - Autobiographical Sketch with Notes, Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 19)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - Outline/Proposal for Autobiographical Book (Box 42, File 20)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - Dark, Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 21)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - Designated Driver, Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 22)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 42, File 23)
- Writings, Manuscripts
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 1)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 2)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 3)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 4)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 5)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - High School Writing Assignments, Daniel C. Prince (Instruction) (Box 43, File 6)
  - Writings, Manuscripts - The Inside Track on Outsider Art and Who Does Self-Taught Art (Box 43, File 7)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Mayhem, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 8)
  - Writings, Manuscripts -- Miscellaneous (Box 43, File 9)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – On The Nose, Daniel C. Prince (Box 43, File 10)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Invoices (Box 43, File 11)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Order Forms, Draft and Blank (Box 43, File 12)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Order Forms (Box 43, File 13)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Order Payments and Notes (Box 43, File 14)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Reviews Fall, 1995, Oct 1995, Nov 1995 (Box 43, File 15)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Reviews, Dec 1995 (Box 43, File 16)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Reviews, Jan 1996, Mar 1996 and Others (Box 43, File 17)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Book Sales Tracking (Box 43, File 18)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Contract (Box 43, File 19)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Correspondence with Peter Ackroyd (Box 43, File 20)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Forward and Introduction (Box 43, File 21)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 1, Alvin Jarrett (Box 43, File 22)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 2, Karolina Danek (Box 43, File 23)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 3, Howard Finster (Box 43, File 24)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 4, Randy Toy (Box 43, File 25)
- Writings, Manuscripts
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 5, Homer Green (Box 44, File 1)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 6, Spot Daniel (Box 44, File 2)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 7, Ray Librizzi (Box 44, File 3)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 8, Ellia Pawlovsky (Box 44, File 4)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 9, Irene Fire (Box 44, File 5)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 10, Larry Armistead (Box 44, File 6)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 11, Joe Hardin (Box 44, File 7)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 12, John Jordan (Box 44, File 8)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 13, Joe Romano (Box 44, File 9)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 14, Ci Ci Saussy (Box 44, File 10)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 15, Rhawn York (Box 44, File 11)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 16, Stephie Mark (Box 44, File 12)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 17, Danny Dowler (Box 44, File 13)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 18, David Secon (Box 44, File 14)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 19, Robert E. Smith (Box 44, File 15)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 20, Jefferey D. Ray (Box 44, File 16)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Draft, Chapter 21, L-15 (Box 44, File 17)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Early Sample Chapter (Box 44, File 18)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Early Sample Outline (Box 44, File 19)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Edits (Box 44, File 20)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Illustration List (Box 44, File 21)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Incomplete (Box 44, File 22)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity – Exhibit Proposals (Box 44, File 23)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity – Lectures, Book signings, Exhibits (Box 44, File 24)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity – Mailing List (Box 44, File 25)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity –Possible Reviews and Bookstore Signings (Box 44, File 26)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity – Press Releases and Newsletters (Box 44, File 27)
- Writings, Manuscripts
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity – Promotional Schedule, Correspondence, and Notes (Box 45, File 1)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity – Radio, Magazine and Museum Contact (Box 45, File 2)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Poems and Lyrics, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 3)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Poems and Lyrics, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 4)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Starry, Starry Night, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 5)
  - Writings – Stiffs on Ice, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Jul 8, 1975 (Box 45, File 6)
  - Writings – Stone and the Woodman, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Mar 24, 1981 (Box 45, File 7)
  - Writings – Time, Material, and Space: Analysis of Howard Finster’s Paradise Garden, Daniel C. Prince Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Jan 29, 1985 (Box 45, File 8)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Two Sheets to the Wind, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 9)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 10)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 11)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 12)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 13)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 14)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 15)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 16)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 17)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 18)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 19)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Tools and Machines) (Box 45, File 20)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 21)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 22)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 23)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 24)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 25)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 26)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 27)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 28)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 29)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Jerry Brown) (Box 45, File 30)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 31)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 32)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled, Daniel C. Prince, Fragment (Box 45, File 33)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Untitled Fragments, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 34)
  - Writings, Essays – The Causes and Effects of the Imperial Coronation of Charlemagne, 1971 (Box 45, File 35)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Vanderbilt University Independent Study, Medieval English Literature (Box 45, File 36)
  - Writings, Essays – Henri Pirenne, 1971 (Box 45, File 37)
  - Writings – Venice, California: Weirdness on Wheels, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Aug 7, 1979 (Box 45, File 38)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Venice, California: Weirdness on Wheels (Box 45, File 39)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – Voices, Daniel C. Prince (Box 45, File 40)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – What You See is What You Get: Neuroscience and Self- Taught Art; Vanderbilt University Press Proposal (Box 45, File 41)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – What You See Is What You Get: Neuroscience and Self- Taught Art; Notes and Research (Box 45, File 42)
  - Writings, Manuscripts – What You See Is What You Get: Neuroscience and Self-Taught Art, Draft Mailed, October 20, 1998 for Copyright (Box 45, File 43)
- Writings, Notebooks
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Antique Iron Notes, Exhibit Layouts, Environments Article, Correspondence, and 20th Century Art (Box 45, File 44)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Assorted Unidentified Stories, Dialog, and loose papers with “Fuzzy” as a character (Box 45, File 45)
- Writings, Notebooks
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Folk Art, Grant Application Draft and Nick Carter (Box 46, File 1)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Connecticut Commission of Arts, Talon, Correspondence, Sketches, Hawaiian Petroglyphs, Outlines and Samples, Press Release, Internship Letter, and Assorted (Box 46, File 2)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Wickham edits, Correspondence, Drawings and Outlines, The Strange Tale of Leonard Hoo, Notes and Sketches, Exhibition Sketched, Ras Quel, Press Releases, Proposals Nick Carter, Venice Story, Assorted (Box 46, File 3)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Nick Carter, Stiffs of Ice, The One That Didn’t Get Away, Wickham Correspondence, The Poolboy and Unidentified Material (Box 46, File 4)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Jimi Coolbreeze and assorted Notes (Box 46, File 5)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Jimi Coolbreeze (Box 46, File 6)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Jimi Coolbreeze, Harp, Nick Carter and an Untitled Story (Box 46, File 7)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, – Nick Carter, Harp, Correspondence about Dan’s Artwork for Sale, Harp, Some Found Art Workshop and Design Materials (Box 46, File 8)
- Writings, Notebooks
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Names, Addresses, Numbers, and Exhibit Layout and Press, Index of Folk Artists, Collections and Books, Sculpture Ideas, Sailors Valentines, Scrimshaw Notes, Sculpture from Junk, Eskimo Notes and Folk Art Sculpture (Box 47, File 1)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Enoch Wickham and Unidentified Story, Slideshow Notes, Langrock Materials, Correspondence and Landmark Exhibit (Box 47, File 2)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Environmental Show, Correspondence, Bibliographic Materials, Stamford Inventory, A Good Likeness Article, and IRS Information (Box 47, File 3)
  - Writings, Notebooks – Miscellaneous Topics, Holyland Text, Correspondence, We Built It Ourselves, Self Taught Art Notes, STAR Travel Proposal, Unidentified Materials, and 2nd Draft Mysteries in the Field and Stream (Box 47, File 4)
- Writings, Novels
  - Writings, Novels – Harp, Play the Blues Till You Die, Daniel C. Prince (Box 47, File 5)
  - Writings, Novels – Harp, Play the Blues Till You Die, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Mar 3, 1980 (Box 47, File 6)
  - Writings, Novels – Harp, Play the Blues Till You Die, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Apr 18, 1980 (Box 47, File 7)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Story Outline andSample Chapters (Box 47, File 8)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Chapter Outlines (Box 47, File 9)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Chapter Outlines (Box 47, File 10)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Chapters 1-3 (Box 47, File 11)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Pages 163-200 Chapter unlabeled (Box 47, File 12)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Draft (Box 47, File 13)
- Writings, Novels
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, First Half Self Bound Copy (Box 48, File 1)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Second Half Self Bound Copy (Box 48, File 2)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for, Aug 23, 1978 (Box 48, File 3)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Mar 3, 1980 (Box 48, File 4)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, Million Dollar Stash, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Apr 18, 1980 (Box 48, File 5)
  - Writings, Novels – Jimi Coolbreeze, Ras Quel and Harp Drafts and Sample Chapters and Outlines Mailed, August 19, 1981 for Copyright (Box 48, File 6)
  - Writings, Novels—Jimi Coolbreeze, The Pool Boy, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Jun 17, 1975 Chapters 1-3 (Box 48, File 7)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Arrogant Assassin (Box 48, File 8)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Dirty Snow (Box 48, File 9)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Chapters 1-4, and summary of remaining chapters, handwritten notes. (Box 48, File 10)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Chapter Outlines (Box 48, File 11)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Chapters 5-7 (Box 48, File 12)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Chapters 1-8, Outline of 9-11 and 14 (Box 48, File 13)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Chapters 1-8 (Box 48, File 14)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Jul 28, 1978 (Box 48, File 15)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Apr 25, 1979 (Box 48, File 16)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Eye of the Hurricane, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for Copyright, Jul 31, 1980 (Box 48, File 17)
- Writings, Novels
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii and Eye of the Hurricane, Drafts, Handwritten in Spiral bound notebook (Box 49, File 1)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Fragments (Box 49, File 2)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince Charter Publications Copyright, 1979 (Box 49, File 3)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Chapters 1-8 (Box 49, File 4)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Chapters 9-12 (Box 49, File 5)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Chapters 13-16 (Box 49, File 6)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Chapters 17-18, Epilogue (Box 49, File 7)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Draft Chapters 1-4 (Box 49, File 8)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Chapters 10-15 (Box 49, File 9)